(Raj:)Hey, we've always talked
(Raj:)about playing together.
(Howard:)Well, it could be fun
(Howard:)to try a little acoustic thing.
(Raj:)Oh, we could play
"filk" music.
(Stuart:)What's that?
(Raj:)It's been around for years.
(Raj:)It's like folk music,
but with a sci-fi/fantasy theme.
(Stuart:)I like it.
(Stuart:)It sounds exactly like something
(Stuart:)I shouldn't be expected
to pay for.
(Raj:)Dude, if we do this,
(Raj:)we're gonna need
a cool band name.
(Howard:)You know, I've actually
(chuckles)
(Howard:)had one I've been
sitting on for years.
(Raj:)Really?
(Howard:)It was for this power trio
(Howard:)I tried to put together
in junior high,
(Howard:)but I was short two friends.
(Raj:)What is it?
(Howard:)Footprints on the Moon.
(Raj:)I just got chills.
(Howard:)So did I.
(Stuart:)Me, too.
But I-I might have Lyme Disease.
(Sheldon:)Just a few more signatures,
and we'll be finished.
(Sheldon:)Initial here to acknowledge
that you've returned your key.